This film is dedicated to you.
SHYAM SINGHA ROY
Don't worry. He just likes to bluster.
Just chill. I'll take care of it.
Okay. Get everything ready.
I'll be right there.
AAKALI RAJYAM
IRUVAR
-Good morning.
-Morning, bro.
-Everyone is here? All set?
-Yes, we are ready.
-Do they have the script?
-Yes.
-Have you explained the scene?
-Yes, I've explained.
Everyone had coffee as well.
Thank you for reminding.
Get me some black coffee.
What are you looking at?
Go and get me some coffee.
-Get into position.
-Yeah, bro.
Hey, what the hell are you doing here?
Don't you have any work to do?
I've been promised a role in the film.
Oh, is it? So that's why you have
groomed yourself like a hero?
You fool! They will put you far away
in the background somewhere.
You'll regret if you take
a filmmaker's words for granted.
Go and get some black coffee.
Leave this here.
If you take two months to complete
the auditions for a short film,
how long would you take
to complete a feature film?
Whatever we do, it must be perfect.
-You're right.
-Pan it to the right.
This is not perfection.
This is called obsession.
By the time you become a director,
you'll surely make me close down my cafe.
Then, I'll have to open a small tea shop
near a film studio.
-That is your plan, right?
-Bro.
More than a 100 people
have come to your cafe for auditions.
We are promoting your brand for free.
What is the name of my cafe?
Coffin!
Coffin? What the heck?
It's Coffee Inn!
-Coffee. Inn.
-Okay.
-Coffin is a box for burying a corpse.
-Okay. Ready. Ask them to come.
-Yes, bro.
Hello.
-Did you read the script?
-Yes.
-Any doubts?
-No.
Ready. Start camera.
Rolling, bro.
Action!
The dialogue is correct.
Now, will you please act it out?
I did act it out.
It's very bland. There's no feeling in it.
Don't mug up the dialogues.
Keep them in your subconscious mind.
Action!
Have you worked as a news anchor?
Yes. How do you know?
We have seen you on TV.
That is not the dialogue!
Read it once again,
and deliver it correctly. Okay?
Actually,
I have worked in many short films.
Also, I was a TikTok star
prior to its ban.
I have never auditioned before.
I can directly come to the shoot.
Is this necessary?
You are more focused on your make-up
than your performance.
You may leave now.
Good. I like it.
Give me some time.
My team will contact you soon.
Hey, that girl is good.
Why don't you cast her?
She is good, but she isn't the perfect fit
for the character.
-She is too cliche.
-This is too much.
She's fair-skinned and tall.
Her dialogue delivery is good.
What else do you want?
To become an actor or actress,
it's not necessary
that one must be fair or tall.
Then?
Body movements. Fine speech.
Purity. Fine expression.
What do you mean by expression?
Body language.
Yeah, yesterday's party was crazy,
but I left early.
Oh yeah! You know what happened?
Yesterday, when we were going back home...
That's the body language.
Hey.
So, exactly after she said that,
we laughed about it.
Yeah.
Good body movements.
The music was great, right?
No, no. She is a drama queen.
Yeah. Later, she started crying
in the cab.
You should have seen the face
of the cab driver. Oh, my God!
He was literally pleading with her.
He was so frightened.
Fine speech.
-Hey, bro!
-Hey!
-Sorry, ma'am.
-Please be careful.
-Relax. Chill.
-Sorry, ma'am.
Don't panic. Here you go.
-Okay?
-Sorry, ma'am.
That's okay.
Purity.
Oh! Okay.
I got to go.
I'll catch up with you guys later.
-Okay, bye.
-Bye.
She's my female lead.
Excuse me.
Hi! Can I have a word with you?
I'm Vasu, a film director.
-Director?
-Yeah.
What movies have you directed?
Tell her.
Upcoming director.
I'm directing a short film now.
If it's successful,
I'll be offered a movie.
Okay.
Nice, I guess. Good luck.
I think it will be great
if you could act in my film.
Oh! Thanks.
But me? Acting in a film?
No way. I'm not interested.
Sorry.
You'll become interested
once you start working.
I've been holding
the auditions for two months.
You are exactly as I imagined
that character.
No... You don't understand.
I'm not at all interested,
so let's leave it here. Okay?
I need to go. Bye.
She is not interested.
-Talk to her.
-Hello!
It's really hard to find
a Telugu-speaking heroine.
Please accept the role.
You can get free coffee here.
This is my cafe.
Bro, relax.
First of all, I don't like movies.
I don't even watch them.
Exactly.
My heroine is also not interested
in movies.
Her physical appearance
is similar to yours.
Big eyes, arrogant attitude,
and average looks.
What the hell!
-I mean...
-I'm not interested, and I'm not doing it.
-Say something, man.
-That's it!
Listen...
Come on, man!
I need to take care of my cafe.
Then I'll continue the auditions
at your place.
Let's go and persuade her.
Hey, what the hell!
What do you think of yourselves?
Don't you get it?
You followed me to my house.
Are you crazy?
This is too much, man. How dare you?
Hey... Relax.
This is not right. I understand.
We've come here
because we're serious about casting you.
We are working hard. Please don't refuse.
What is this ruckus? Who are they?
Dad, they have followed me
all the way from a cafe.
He is trying to persuade me
despite my rejection.
I'll call the she-team.
Hey...
You look like a decent guy.
What do you do?
Film director.
Film director? What movies have you made?
It's okay.
Upcoming director.
Oh! But I don't want to marry
my daughter off to a movie man.
Sorry, you can find someone else.
I know, people don't even want to rent out
their houses to movie people.
-Your daughter...
-Name is Keerti.
I'm asking Keerti to act in my short film.
Short film?
Will you release it on YouTube?
-I just want to show it to a producer...
-It'll be on YouTube.
-Your daughter can be part of it.
-Is it? What other films has he made?
Ms. Keerti, listen to me.
Your dad has approved.
Now you must agree to it.
Why should I?
This is my last option.
I don't have any other choice.
If you don't agree,
I'll tell your dad that you smoke.
What the hell?
My dad won't believe you.
Are you for real?
Please, Keerti. I'll delete it.
Please understand my desperation.
I'm really sorry for troubling you.
This is really important for me.
This short film is very crucial
to my career.
And I can't afford to hire
professional actors.
Films have been my passion
since childhood.
My budget is low.
I've resigned my software job as well.
Please understand.
But I don't know how to act.
Acting is nothing but reacting.
Your reactions are naturally good.
You are a natural star.
It's just a short film, dear.
Everyone is making them these days.
Our neighbor uploads all her recipes
on YouTube.
I secretly follow her channel.
Is he stalking that lady?
I get to see you on screen
when you're away.
Please accept.
Okay, I'll do it. But I'll leave Hyderabad
in two weeks.
-I'm going to Mumbai for higher studies.
-All the best.
She is pursuing
her master's in psychology.
Is that why she behaves like a psycho?
So I can give you only two weeks.
I've even booked my flight tickets.
Two weeks is more than enough.
And one more thing.
If anything troubles me during the shoot,
-I'll immediately opt out of it.
-No...
Don't worry. We'll take great care of you.
You'll not be troubled in the slightest.
And...
What about that photo?
Deleted. Deleted.
I'll pick you up at 6 am.
What photo is that?
Photo... Selfie!
Uncle, let's take a selfie. Please.
Hello.
What?
-Good morning.
Oh, my God!
Do you have a make-up artist?
Where is the make-up artist?
What make-up artist?
That guy...
Oh! He died of CoVID 19.
Please do your own make-up.
Make-up is set.
The story is...
She loves to paint from childhood.
Canvas is her world.
But her painting lacks soul.
She searches for a color in every emotion.
All of a sudden,
she finds a blank paper one day.
This take is okay.
Continue... Okay.
Nice. You are doing great.
Shall we go for the next scene?
Change your costume.
Ready.
Hey, where shall I change my dress?
Well, you can use my car.
I'll cover the car with a black cloth.
What the hell?
I don't even use
the fitting rooms at a clothes store.
And you are asking me to change
my dress on a highway? Impossible!
Keerti, films have been my passion
since childhood.
My budget is low.
I've even resigned my job.
Please understand.
What are you looking at?
Bro, it's about to rain.
Good. We can use the rain effect for free.
It costs a lot to artificially create one.
Will the actress agree to it?
Okay. Rolling!
Action!
Oh, shit.
Keerti... Keep walking...
Be in the mood!
Slowly look at the sky
and cry your heart out.
More. More.
Cut!
Nice.
One more!
The house looks great.
-Keep it in top angle. A nice shot.
-Okay.
Tell them to turn those lights off.
It's the police.
Are you shooting a film?
Do you have a permit?
-It's just a short film, sir.
-It doesn't matter.
We have received a complaint from the MP.
What's his problem with us?
He saw a drone flying around his house.
Come to the station.
You can take us, but leave the girl alone.
Oh! She is with you!
I thought she was related to the MP.
-Bhadram.
-Sir.
-Get her into the car.
-Okay, sir.
And then what?
Don't take my cap.
Sorry, sir.
I'll make sure this never happens again.
Keerti! Keerti...
Why should I put up
with a crazy movie guy?
I am a graduate in psychology.
Why should I get myself detained
at police stations because of you?
-Just go to hell.
-Okay.
Okay.
I've skipped this month's rent
to pay for the shoot.
I don't have enough budget
to hire a new actress.
It will stall the shooting of my film.
So be it!
So be it. It's all right.
Films have been my passion
since childhood.
My budget is low.
I've resigned my job as well.
-Please, understand. This short film--
-I understand.
Your career requires me to suffer.
Stop your theatrics. I'll do it.
Thank you, Keerti!
Thank you, uncle.
Thank god she's agreed to work
with me again.
Thank you. Come, let's go.
Such an idiot.
-Tomorrow is the last day of the shoot.
-Yeah, bye.
Bye.
-Bye.
-Hi, ma'am.
-Hello, ma'am.
We've been waiting to take
a selfie with you.
Why?
Aren't you the heroine of this film?
Yes, I am.
Keshav, go back two steps.
-Don't be shy. Come closer.
-All right.
Hey, stop it!
-Bro...
-One second.
Wait for two counts, then
immediately take camera favor.
What are you doing?
Don't you have manners?
-Do you think I'm--
-Do you want us to buy a ticket for this?
Bro.
How dare you touch me?
Hold this.
Come, let's take a selfie.
No...
Vasu...
Vasu!
What's happening? Who are these guys?
-Sachin, what happened here?
-Bro...
You ear is bleeding.
Are you okay?
Hey, what's wrong?
The tripod! It cost us Rs. 15,000.
How did it break?
You acted like a hero and broke it.
First, let's get out of here.
VARNAM
-Congrats, Vasu.
-Sir.
Well done! Nice!
You dealt with the subject maturely.
Thank you, sir.
-We shall work together.
-Yes, sir.
Get him to sign the agreement
and pay him an advance.
Meet me when you have
the bound script ready.
I'll get it done within a month.
-Good luck.
-Thank you, sir.
It's almost done, sir.
I'll give it to you tomorrow morning.
Okay, sir.
TALK TO YOUR PARENTS ABOUT OUR MARRIAGE
Amazing.
It's a great script, Vasu.
The climax is just mind-blowing.
I can put money on this.
Thank you, sir.
You are a very good writer.
You can start the project now.
I'll assign you a team.
Thank you, sir.
Here you go.
Let's wait a little longer.
Wait for what? It'll lose the chillness.
I'm waiting for Keerti.
You carry on.
Hi, Keerti.
Wow!
So excited to meet her?
You...
Hi, Keerti.
Are you pulling my leg again?
-Hi.
Nice view.
What is in that bag?
Did you bring some snacks?
A small gift for you.
For me? It's not really necessary.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
I'm really happy for you.
It's very nice.
Vasu, mention a special thanks to me
in the credits of your feature film.
I'll be your lucky charm.
Not just my name, but also add my photo.
Photo is added if the person is dead.
Shall I do it?
No need.
You guys are unbelievable.
I despised you guys in the beginning,
but now I'll miss you all.
Please be in touch.
You will leave for Mumbai.
This guy will ignore us
once he starts working on his new film.
I'll be all alone, selling coffee.
Stop your theatrics.
He will surely forget me.
Do you think I'll forget you?
Impossible.
In that case,
wear the shirt that I've just gifted you
when you succeed as a director.
Then I will believe
that you still remember me.
Done.
Okay. I'll leave.
Hey, kid. Come, let's go.
-Bye.
-See you. Bye. Nice.
How long will you stay here?
I'll leave in another five minutes.
Cool.
Keerti, tell your friends
to keep visiting my cafe.
-I'll give them a ten percent discount.
-Okay.
-See you.
-Don't roam around, go home.
To your home!
Okay. It's about to rain. Get inside.
So?
When will we meet again?
I don't know.
Sorry.
I didn't get you a gift.
Bye.
Rosie.
What the fuck!
-What happened?
-Who is Rosie?
I thought you were a gentleman.
Such a pervert!
Keerti, what's wrong?
How can you think about another girl
when you are sharing a bed with me?
You should be ashamed!
This is the psychology of men.
You can never truly love one girl.
You men are dogs.
Keerti...
I'm really sorry.
Rosie?
I don't know any Rosie.
It's just a slip of the tongue.
Just shut up and get lost.
It was stupid of me
to fall in love with you.
This is so embarrassing.
I never want to see your face again.
Rosie?
Who is Rosie?
I don't know.
Tell me the truth.
It's the truth.
I've never heard that name...
-Rosie.
-I've never heard it before.
-Then why did you say call her Rosie?
-I don't know.
You must have picked that name
from some shitty Hollywood film.
And you called her by that name.
She won't take it easy.
Shit!
What do I do now?
After years of struggle, you've got
an opportunity to make a feature film.
Concentrate on that.
Rolling!
Action!
Silence!
UNIKI
Are you nervous?
That's a small word
to describe my feelings now.
I don't even know how to describe it.
It's a ten-year dream,
and one whole year of hard work.
Bro, the show has just ended.
Bro, how do you like the movie?
It's great. I loved it. A blockbuster!
The movie is a hit! Congratulations, dude!
Congratulations.
Bro, he is the director of this film.
You are the director of the film!
The movie is amazing. A blockbuster.
The climax was mind-blowing!
Bro, can I take a selfie with you?
Please, let me take a selfie.
Okay, keep moving.
Slowly.
Please keep moving.
Why are you crying like a baby?
Your film is a hit.
Vasu, I just got a call from Mumbai.
Producer Vishal Chaturvedi
has seen our movie.
He wants to remake it in Hindi.
Wow!
And they want you
to direct the Hindi version as well.
-Are you serious? A Bollywood film?
-Bro, this is crazy!
You are one lucky guy.
You will be reaching greater heights.
Let's celebrate. Open the bottle!
MUMBAI
KOLKATA
Welcome to all of you.
Well, I'm super excited and happy
to introduce a south Indian sensation,
Mr. Vasudev, to the Hindi cinema.
I must say that his last film
was a super-duper blockbuster hit.
Uniki.
UNIKI
Well, we are about
to make it now in Hindi.
Background?
He has no godfather in the industry.
He is a nobody.
I've got some more great news
to share with all of you.
We're gonna be making two more
very high budget films with him.
Mr. Vasudev?
We have an arrest warrant against you.
You have to come with us.
Arrest warrant? What?
Come on. Let's go.
Well, this is a shocking news for us.
Our company doesn't entertain
this kind of stuff.
I'm calling this announcement off.
HE COPIED FROM BENGALI,
AND NOT KOREAN OR HOLLYWOOD!
Yes, Dad.
Why?
Okay. I'll call you back.
DIRECTOR VASU ARRESTED DURING PRESS MEET
Bro, please tell me if you know
any good lawyers.
It's about the director who got arrested.
Yes, he is my friend.
No, he is a good guy.
He is framed by someone.
Okay. Please let me know
if you find any good lawyers.
Okay. Bye.
She is Padmavati, my cousin.
Oh.
Nobody in my family likes her.
We always fought each other.
Then why did you bring me to her?
She was a gold-medalist in college.
-Good morning, ma'am.
-Good morning.
I need help with the drunk driving charges
against me.
The breath analyzer showed 300 points.
Who drinks that much?
Even if the judge lets you go, I won't.
Hi, Paddu. How are you?
I'm a bit irritated.
How are your parents?
I don't know.
I haven't met them in a long time.
I have been meaning to meet you
for a long time.
But I couldn't.
I know that none of my relatives want to
meet me unless they need some legal help.
What can I do for you?
As I told you, it's about
my friend, Vasu, the film director.
Oh! Yes. I saw it on the news.
He was arrested during a press meet.
He is your friend! So sad.
Yes, ma'am. You must help him out.
What do you do?
I own a cafe.
Do you provide a free service to
all your customers or do you charge them?
We charge them.
I understand.
Of course. Tell me how much you charge.
I will pay you.
I will.
But first, I need to meet the accused.
He is in the police station.
Let's go, please.
You are right.
You shouldn't meet her often.
Hi, Vasu. I am Padmavati, your lawyer.
What's happening? Why did they arrest me?
India's largest publication house,
SR Publishers, has lodged
a case of copyright infringement
against you.
They have alleged that your scripts
and the story of your film
have been plagiarized
from their Telugu and Bengali books.
What?
Nonsense.
I've studied your case.
I'll come to the point.
If you plead guilty to your crime
without wasting the court's time,
your punishment could be reduced.
Since this is not a grave crime
like murder or rape,
you can get away
with a mere six-month sentence
or with just a fine, if you are lucky.
I should plead guilty?
Who told you that I'm guilty?
I'm not apologizing to anyone.
I did not plagiarize from any book.
I wrote those stories.
Two years ago, I registered them
with the Telugu Writers Association.
I have proof.
These books were published 50 years ago.
Your stories match theirs exactly.
You didn't even have the sense
to change the names of the characters
while copying from them.
They are exactly the same.
Even a kid can tell
that you have copied from this book.
Look, I'd lose my cool if you keep saying
that I copied someone's work.
I've never read these books.
And I don't know Bengali either.
One should never lie
to a doctor or lawyer.
I'm here to help you.
Are you my lawyer or the opponent's?
Why are you forcing me to plead guilty?
I didn't plagiarize. Why don't you get it?
Hey! Keep your voice down.
It's not about me.
We have to prove to the court
that you didn't plagiarize.
As a lawyer,
it's your responsibility to prove it.
There's nothing to prove.
The evidence is against you.
Quit if you can't do it.
I'll get another lawyer.
Okay. Good luck.
Okay. Fuck off! What the...
I can't deal with him.
Hire another lawyer.
-He's too adamant.
-What happened?
It's a simple open and shut case.
I can't help him if he doesn't cooperate.
He's really important to me.
Please don't give up on him.
Really? What is he to you?
Your boyfriend?
It's a long story.
Okay. None of my business.
Well, I can get a bail order for him.
But I can't take up this case.
His opponent's lawyer
is Mr. Krishnamurthy.
To go up against him is nothing less
than hitting a dead wall. Impossible.
You know, I have his photo in my office.
Why?
He is my inspiration.
I aspire to become a lawyer like him.
If you want to become as great as him,
you have to beat a lawyer of his stature.
Now you have that opportunity.
Please think about it.
"Copyright case OS no. 234 of 2021,"
"complainant SR Publishers
accused on Vasudev Ghanta."
Yes, proceed.
Your Honor, my client, SR Publishers,
is a leading publishing house
in the country.
They have contributed a lot
to the growth of literature
in our country, Your Honor.
Now, coming to the point,
the issue here is,
this man here, named Vasudev
plagiarized from Astitva,
which is my client's intellectual property
and a best-selling novel.
The accused converted it into a script,
and made a movie out of it.
That is not all, Your Honor.
He has plagiarized two more books,
converted them into scripts,
and sold them
to a Bollywood production house.
Mr. Vasudev did that.
These stories were authored
by a legendary Bengali-Telugu writer,
who shook the entire nation
and the government alike
with his writings in the 1970s.
His name is Shyam Singha Roy.
I'm submitting to the court
the copies of the original novel
and the plagiarized script by Mr. Vasudev.
Please.
WHERE THERE IS DHARMA,
THERE WILL BE VICTORY
UNIKI
ASTITVA
Your Honor, it's a color-able imitation
of the original
with the sole purpose of deriving profits.
It's a direct infringement of three novels
which are copyright properties
of my client, SR Publishers.
So now, on behalf of my client,
under section 63
of the copyright act 1957,
I hereby demand that Mr. Vasu
be sentenced to five years of imprisonment
and a penalty of Rs. 10 crores
be levied upon him.
Also, a 50 percent share in the revenue
generated by the plagiarized film
should be granted to my client.
That'll be all for now, Your Honor.
Thank you so much.
Defense.
You may put forward your case.
-Plead guilty.
-Impossible.
Your Honor, this is a false accusation.
My client doesn't accept this accusation.
We plead not guilty.
My client is innocent until proven guilty.
The court has verified
the copies of both the works.
98 percent of the content
is exactly the same.
How could he have written it
without plagiarizing?
I don't believe it's a coincidence.
The prima facie evidence is sufficient
for the court to believe that he's guilty.
Then how do you defend
and prove your innocence?
I don't know
why both the works are the same.
But I can tell you this,
I didn't copy my stories from any book.
My stories are my creation.
You can conduct a lie detection test
if you want.
What? This is not a movie. Lie detection
tests are not approved just like that.
-What do you...
-Your Honor...
Let's do that.
It will save everyone's time.
Let's go ahead
with the lie detection test.
Defense?
That is the request from the defense, sir.
Okay.
According to the section 45,
selection of evidence,
the court authorizes
the forensic department
to conduct a lie detection test
on Mr. Vasudev.
The forensic department has concluded
that Mr. Vasudev is not lying.
Your Honor, the lie detection test
can only be considered
as corroborative evidence
but not as complete evidence.
I'm sure the defense
is well aware about this.
It is not impossible
to cheat the lie detection test.
The accused is yet
to prove himself innocent.
Until then, the charges against
Mr. Vasudev will remain valid.
That's all, Your Honor.
Your Honor, we need more time
to prove my client's innocence.
To look deep into the issue
and gather more evidence.
I also request for an unconditional bail
for my client.
Your Honor,
I object to the unconditional bail.
Overruled.
The court grants
unconditional bail to Mr. Vasudev
and also grants a period of three days
to the defense to submit further evidence.
Until then, the court is adjourned.
How are you?
I'm fine.
This shirt looks good on you.
I got arrested after wearing it.
But...
Thank you.
I am the one who got you bail.
You should be thanking me.
First, you need to trust me.
Then, I'll thank you.
How can I trust you?
Your work exactly matches
the content of those books.
I don't get it either.
How can they be so similar?
Give me those books.
Shyam Singha Roy.
I think the 'SR' in SR Publishers
stands for Singha Roy.
I have studied this family.
Shyam's mother was a Telugu,
and father a Bengali.
Theirs was a love marriage.
They settled in West Bengal.
Shyam had three siblings
and he was the youngest.
He was born in a village called Kalikapur
in the Kharagpur district of West Bengal.
He became a famous writer
and a renowned social activist in Kolkata.
Post the year 1977,
there is no information available
on his whereabouts.
If he is assumed dead,
no one knows where his grave is.
In 1985, his three brothers
met with a tragic car accident.
The children of those dead brothers
are currently running the company.
They filed the case against you.
There are no photos of Shyam
except for the paintings in these books.
Since his mother was a Telugu,
Shyam was well-versed in Telugu as well.
He wrote books in Telugu too.
TRAITOR
NAXALBARI
TO MY BELOVED GOPAL
Keri, a 10-year-old girl, was
donated by her father to a temple.
"Her father donated her"
"to a temple."
Vasu.
Your ear is bleeding again.
Why is he bleeding?
Sometimes he gets zoned out.
And he forgets his surroundings.
Whenever that happens,
he bleeds from his ear.
How many times has it happened before?
Many times.
It happened on the day when we fought.
Once while writing this script.
While shooting the short film.
And a few more times.
We even consulted a doctor.
He did some tests and said
that it was the result of stress.
He was working on his first film.
He never slept properly the whole time.
Strange.
Yes, ma'am. I really think
something is wrong with him.
What do you think?
A human mind is as mysterious
as the whole universe.
Nobody knows the infinite secrets
that are hidden within.
Human consciousness
is an ocean full of secrets.
How do you propose we unearth
the secrets of Vasu's mind?
We can try clinical hypnosis on him.
Hypnosis?
Yeah. With hypnotherapy,
there is a chance to know what happens
inside Vasu's brain
during those blackouts.
Okay, ma'am. One final request.
This is a sensitive case.
So I urge you to deal
with this matter personally.
Sure.
Our print sales are declined by 23...
Excuse us.
He is out on bail.
Also, he passed the lie detection test.
Uncle!
Is it Shyam's story?
Yes, Uncle.
Sit.
Hi, Vasu.
From our conversation,
I have noted down the dates
when you experienced those blackouts.
Vasu, I'm going to start
the procedure now.
Just relax.
Take a deep breath in.
Inhale and exhale all your worries out.
Follow my voice and look at the monitor.
This book is your life.
Do you know today's date?
August 17th.
Do you remember the day
when you were arrested?
Last Thursday.
When was your film released?
July 7th.
Vasu.
Let's go a little back.
Do you remember the date
when you finished your script?
October 19th.
Vasu, what happened on that day?
I had to submit my script the next day.
However hard I tried,
I wasn't able to write the climax.
I felt a severe headache.
I felt dizzy.
My whole body felt very heavy.
And?
Come on, Vasu. Try harder.
Try to remember.
What happened after that?
What did you do?
Try hard, Vasu. You can do it.
Rosie.
Rosie?
Who is Rosie? How is she related to you?
My wife.
Vasu?
She's my wife.
Did Rosie give you these Bengali books?
These books were not published then.
ASTITVA - NAXALBARI
What do you mean?
What year are we talking about?
1969.
What is your name?
Shyam Singha Roy.
1969, KALIKAPUR, WEST BENGAL,
MONTH OF ASHWAYUJA, RIVER GANGES
Please give me some water.
Sister, give me some water.
What's the matter?
Why don't you go and fetch yourself
some water instead of asking everyone?
We aren't supposed to touch the well, sir.
Did the well forbid you?
You can either wait for the rains,
or you can pluck up some courage.
Hey, Shyam!
He is a pariah.
He cannot touch the water from the well.
-What does that mean?
-He is beneath us.
The water comes from the ground
which is beneath our feet.
He is low caste.
Shouldn't he get thirsty then?
Water is not owned
by any particular caste.
He was born and raised in this village.
He belongs to this very land.
The same land grows the food
which your children eat.
He is an untouchable.
Then why are you walking
on the land that he walks on?
Why are you breathing the same air
that he breathes? Stop breathing!
Land, air, and water
are life-preserving resources.
They don't abide by the evil caste system.
You can't impose caste hierarchy anymore.
This isn't the age of Rigveda.
We now live in independent India.
An Ambedkar has arrived here!
You can write these ideas in your books.
Maybe we read them sometime.
If you dare touch the water,
we will burn down your hut,
and then, we'll skin you alive.
Sir, we don't want water.
We will go away.
Now, this well is untouchable as well.
This belongs to him.
Those who are thirsty
can still draw water from here.
Those who want to abide by caste
can die of thirst.
Before you go near his hut,
do keep in mind
that I know where your house is.
Beware!
Very good.
Well done, comrade.
Friend, come and join us.
One bullet can kill only one person.
Whereas one written word can mobilize
millions of people.
"The sky is covered with clouds
and the sun has gone down."
"Kuku went to fetch water
from the Padma Dighi sector."
It's Padma riverbank.
Padma...
Riverbank.
Your father taught me this song
when I was your age.
I'd sit on his lap and learn.
Now it's my responsibility
to pass it on to you guys.
What have you done this time, Shyam?
Your brother is very angry with you.
What did I do?
Have I done something?
Dadabhai is coming back from Kharagpur.
Be careful with him.
No matter what he says to you,
don't talk back to him.
Have some of this sacred food.
Do not fight during the festivities.
What's the matter?
Is it about today's incident?
Or yesterday's incident?
Or about the one from the day before?
Sit here.
Do you realize what you are doing?
You bring dishonor to our family.
You threw a Dalit into the well.
Are you out of your mind?
They will banish us from this village.
Don't worry about that, brother.
I'll leave this place.
This is a place where some humans
are treated as filth by fellow humans.
I can't stay here.
Go away.
Join those low-caste people
and dream of bringing a revolution.
I've heard that you're mixing
with those armed revolutionaries.
If I wanted to join them,
I could find my way
to their base in the forest.
My principles are different.
Your principles and books
are good for nothing.
Selfishness is the hallmark of human life.
I agree. Selfishness is a great virtue.
You care for your family.
That's selfishness.
I care about the world around me.
That's my selfishness.
Shyam?
Don't be upset that he hit you.
He's our elder brother.
I am not upset with our brother.
I am upset about the society.
It's not just one village,
this problem plagues the whole country.
Only literature can bring about
a change in society.
Shyam.
I have to go. And I must write.
Have you packed already?
Don't tell anyone.
I bought the ticket for the Howrah Express
three days ago.
Festivities are going on.
Can't you wait until it is over?
The festival will come again next year.
Lost time will never come back.
Anyway, I'm an atheist.
I'll leave at midnight
when everyone is asleep.
Please ask sister-in-law
to pack me some rasgullas.
Shyam.
Quit smoking.
It's empty now. I've quit it.
Be careful.
Write us a letter as soon as you reach.
Hey!
Do you know where the boatman is?
It's the first day
of Navaratri festivities.
He must be in the temple
along with the others.
Bro, are you looking for me?
It's getting late. Let's go.
Girls, move quickly.
There is a crowd behind us. Move quickly.
You danced very well.
-Move...
-Please bless my child.
Move it.
Girls, don't be late.
Come on.
Bro, let's go.
Why are they taking them inside?
They are devadasis
who migrated from Bangladesh.
The wives of the deity.
No man is supposed
to lay his eyes on them.
They are held captive in there.
They come to the temple to dance,
and then again go back.
They offer many services inside.
They entertain and satisfy the deity
with their dance and whatnot.
Hey, wait!
Look, girls. All of you get up.
Stand in a line.
Mahant is here.
That girl.
Look here.
Get her ready soon.
If it's delayed, I will see to your end.
Faster. Move.
There are people following us.
Come on, move fast.
What happened?
Move your feet.
Quickly. What are you looking at?
Girls, get in quickly.
You dance beautifully.
I need to talk to you.
Will you come out with me?
What's your name?
Hey, Maitreyi! Come, move it.
Come on, make it fast.
What are you looking at?
Maitreyi.
Come.
What's the matter?
Why aren't you asleep yet?
What are you thinking?
Shashi, do you know
what happened out there?
A guy asked me to go out with him.
Go out?
I mean, to go outside the temple.
-Are you serious?
-Hush!
Yes.
Are you going?
Going where?
You know we can't do that.
How dare he ask me to go out with him!
He must have considered us normal humans.
Had I been in your place,
I would've gone away with him right then.
Of course, you would.
If someone listens to our conversation,
we will be punished and locked up.
Go to sleep.
Anyway, how can we go out with a stranger?
Higher! Higher!
Didn't you leave for Kolkata
to write your books?
What's the hurry?
Let the nine-day festivities get over.
Since when did you turn into a theist?
It's not theism.
It's love.
THIRD NIGHT
Thus Binodini, a devadasi,
spent her entire life in the temple
and attained the path to heaven.
Didn't Binodini
ever step out of the temple threshold?
No.
Why?
It is our culture, a devadasi,
wife of a deity,
is not supposed to leave
the shelter of God.
Isn't this whole world a shelter of God?
So, what's wrong if they come out?
Poor Binodini!
She could never experience the beauty
of this world, which your God created.
Instead of living a 100 years as a slave,
living one day as a free human being
is more meaningful.
Everyone, come and take the sacred food.
Come to the south entrance at 10 pm.
I'll be waiting for you.
I thought you must have left.
I knew you would come.
I don't want to go out.
I came here to see
if you were really waiting here.
Okay.
Come.
Maitreyi!
That's the name the temple gave you.
What's the name your parents gave you?
I'll have to ask them if I ever meet them.
How do you know Telugu?
The teachers from Andhra taught me
Kuchipudi dance and Telugu.
I learned Tamil along with Bharatanatyam.
I learned Malayalam
along with Mohiniyattam.
Also, I know Odiya, Assamese,
and Sanskrit too.
Do you know how to row a boat?
No.
I'll teach you.
Hold this.
There are two ways to do
any activity in this world.
One, with fear.
And the other...
With love.
Just like the way you dance.
What do you do?
I'm a writer.
I write.
What do you write?
The things I need to tell this world.
How will you tell this world about me?
Milky cheeks...
The skin that radiates a golden glow...
The eyes that resemble a child in fear...
Flowy hair...
The figure,
that of a finely chiseled sculpture...
Dances like a peacock...
A maiden who never tasted
the love of her parents...
Living in companionship with a rock...
Though the body has been violated
in the name of God,
yet the heart is filled with holiness.
It's almost dawn.
I have to go. Please take me back.
Time just flies by while talking with you.
By the way, what's your name?
Shyam.
Shyam Singha Roy.
FOURTH NIGHT
FIFTH NIGHT
He is Manoj Singha Roy,
my third elder brother.
My eldest brother is like a father figure,
whereas he is like a mother to me.
This is my friend.
Hello.
Who are you related to?
She is related to God.
SIXTH NIGHT
She is...
The glimmer in her eyes,
The shimmer on her cheeks
Shyam...
You're like a rose that spreads beauty
and bliss while surrounded by thorns.
Today onwards your name is...
Rosie!
NINTH NIGHT
Come away with me, Rosie.
I come out with you every day.
Not like this.
Get out of this captivity
and come into my life.
Come to Kolkata with me.
We shall get married
and start a new life together.
Shyam, don't forget that I am a devadasi.
A woman is a slave to none.
And the one who desires enslavement
can never be God.
This is human slavery
under the guise of God.
Forget it.
Tell me, are you happy?
Do you want to live like a slave?
There are no other festivities
in my life except these nine nights.
Nobody wishes to lead such a life.
We live it out thinking
this is what destiny has in store for us.
Nothing is superior to one's self-respect.
There is nothing wrong in standing up
for what is right.
Only cowards talk about destiny.
Why do you undermine your own value?
Ridiculous!
How can I say what my worth is?
My life was bartered for a sack of rice,
that is my worth.
A sculpture in that temple
is worthier than me.
Your worth cannot be determined by
any one, no matter who they are.
It is what you believe,
the belief that you have in yourself.
Can I survive in the outside world?
Will this society accept me
if I leave the temple?
Tell me.
Have you heard about MS Subbalakshmi?
She was a devadasi too.
But today she is a Padma Bhushan awardee.
Balasaraswathi,
the greatest Bharatanatyam dancer in India
belongs to a devadasi family.
You have mastered
the art of classical dance.
I am with you, and always will be.
You can have a life that you desire.
You need not fear anyone.
I'll be waiting for you.
Across this river,
there is a world awaiting our arrival.
VIJAYADASHAMI
Careful, hold this. Over here.
Oh, God. You are so badly injured.
I'm so sorry for this.
Here...
Careful.
What happened?
Be careful.
Girls, where are you?
Come fast.
Mahant is here.
Come, stand in line.
Come fast.
That girl.
Let go of me. I won't come.
Leave me, I won't come.
I won't go.
I don't want to go.
We won't come.
We are wives of God.
It means, we are like goddesses.
We are not sculptures
that anyone can lay hands on.
We are human beings.
Nobody owns us.
Not even the God.
How dare you speak against me!
You are not a slave of God,
but you're a slave of mine.
Mahant's word is always final.
Go from that side.
Hey! Move fast.
Who the hell are you?
How dare you!
Catch him.
Don't let him get away.
Every woman is as sacred
as a temple sanctum.
What should be done to the wild dog
that contaminates a temple sanctum?
A woman is not a slave to anyone.
Not even to God.
Beware!
Get down.
Come on, get down.
DAINIK BANGLA
ROYAL PRESS PROP. SAYAN SARKAR
Yes?
I need some work.
I can give you a job without pay.
But I will take care of food
and accommodation.
In that case, we are two people.
Oh.
Grandpa asked me to give this to you.
They'll be here in an hour.
I don't know how to cook.
Can I have one more rasgulla?
-Do you want to learn to dance?
-Yes.
You can never bear a child.
I'm very sorry.
Why do you need kids?
Am I not enough?
Type this and compose
the rest of the text.
I'll check it.
Sir.
I have written an article on the topic
that you've been working on.
Would you like to see it once?
Show me.
What nonsense have you written?
You can't just write
whatever comes to your mind.
Print this one.
You are a great writer.
And I take full responsibility of printing
your first book.
Thank you.
ASTITVA
Hey, congratulations!
The book became a huge success.
We're arresting you for writing
against the government.
Red salute to the revolutionaries!
Start printing.
Royalty checks.
Let's buy a piece of land
and build our own house.
What's the matter, Rosie?
I was lucky to find you
and I escaped from their captivity.
If there were 25 devadasis
in just one temple,
in temples across the nation,
just imagine how many devadasis
must be living under subjugation.
But society doesn't have
any regard for them.
Who will liberate them
from their struggles?
Who is responsible
for their children's future?
TRAITOR
In a community where a woman
sells her flesh to feed herself,
all men from that community are impotent.
Women are not a commodity!
ASTITVA
TO DOWN WITH SHYAM SINGHA ROY
I AM A FAN OF YOUR IDEAS
Many more are coming.
We can't accommodate them all here.
I'm planning to provide housing
and jobs to those who can work,
and a pension for those who can't work.
Even the government will help me in this.
I have no worries in my mind.
It is as clear as this moonless sky.
Is this what we call happiness?
Shyam, you know what?
It is said that a devadasi who dies on
a new moon day will be unified with God.
Whenever death comes knocking at my door--
I want to die on a new moon day like this,
lying on your lap,
staring at you in my last moments
with a smile on my lips.
That's my final wish.
Our elder brother is unwell.
He wants to see you.
Will you come home once?
I'm scared of that village.
After all that has happened there,
I don't feel good about
you going back to that village.
Don't go, Shyam.
I lost my parents in my childhood.
My brother has been
a father figure to me since then.
I have to go, Rosie.
Fear shouldn't constrain
my love for my family.
Take care. Even if it takes a while...
I promise,
I'll be back.
I read your books without
the knowledge of our brothers.
I've collected all your books.
I'm your biggest fan.
What are you writing? Is it a new story?
A short story.
I've just got the idea.
Read it and tell me your opinion.
Sister-in-law, Shyam is here!
Everybody come here.
How are you?
I'm fine. How are you?
I'm good. Have some food.
Serve him food.
Hurry up.
Go and get some coconuts from the market.
I'll get some rasgullas as well, okay?
Take care of him.
Why is the house so silent?
Where are the kids?
They are in Kharagpur,
pursuing their studies there.
How are you, Sister-in-law?
What happened?
Are you all right?
Nothing like that. Have your food, Shyam.
Sit.
You may go inside.
How is your health, Brother?
Fine.
Everybody is talking about you.
I read about you
in the newspapers as well.
You have become a great person.
I haven't read any of your books.
I don't like your thoughts anyway.
But you have done well in your life,
that's good enough for me.
We can't do away with blood relationships.
I can't keep you away.
I've arranged a match for you,
from our caste.
Meet her once, and then get married.
You can continue
your social service from here.
I'm already married, Brother.
If this is what you wanted to discuss,
then I'm done with it.
We will never accept that prostitute
as a daughter-in-law in this house.
She's my wife.
Rosie Singha Roy.
If you speak ill of her once again,
I'd make you pay for it.
Beware!
You revolted against our traditions
and left this village.
And because you belong to this family
and we are your siblings,
the people here are treating us
like untouchables.
Only your death can guarantee
a good future for our children.
We can regain our honor in this village
by putting you to death.
Shyam!
What did you do to him? Shyam!
I promised her that I would come back.
Oh, God!
Shyam!
I have made a mistake, Shyam!
I need to go to Kolkata.
Who are you?
What do you want?
The press owner, Sayan Sarkar.
He is my grandfather.
Sarada?
A dance teacher named Rosie
used to live here.
Rosie?
Our Rosie?
Nobody came looking for Rosie
in all these years.
Are you a relative of hers?
I'm a very close relative of hers.
There was nobody to look after the trust.
Hence it was shut down.
Many of them
were left in a helpless situation.
Some of them chose to switch back
to their previous livelihood,
for the sake of their children.
A few families have managed to survive
in Sonagachi.
I was very small then.
I don't clearly remember,
but a few days after
her husband Shyam's disappearance,
Rosie too left this place,
and went away searching for Shyam.
The last news was that both of them
were killed in their village.
Vasu, we need to be in the court tomorrow.
Your Honor...
I'm really sorry, Your Honor.
But in my career of close
to about 35 years,
I've never seen something
as preposterous or as absurd as this.
Rebirth!
Finding no other way
to disprove their crime,
they are presenting
such a third-rate concept in court.
The accused is a filmmaker, Your Honor.
He shot a video
and he is playing that as evidence.
Your Honor, this isn't the 16th century.
We are in the 21st century.
If we accept such videos as evidence,
tomorrow someone else, claiming to be
the reincarnation of Dhirubhai Ambani,
might lay claim to the ownership
of Reliance Industries.
But just to humbly remind
the honorable court, Your Honor,
hypnotherapy is not medically approved
in India.
-Isn't it so, professor?
-Yes, but--
That's it.
So, Your Honor,
I will conclude with two things.
Hypnosis results cannot be considered
as evidence in any case.
And, the idea of reincarnation
is a superstition.
There is no scientific proof for that.
That'll be all, Your Honor.
With that, I rest my case. Thank you.
You may leave now, ma'am.
Mr. Krishnamurthy...
What is that on your forehead?
That's a religious mark. So?
As you are a devotee of Lord Vishnu,
I don't need to remind you this.
When people demanded to build
a temple in Ayodhya for Lord Rama,
the seventh incarnation of Lord Vishnu,
the Supreme Court of India
permitted them to do so,
but never asked for scientific proof
for Lord Rama's existence,
nor did it dismiss it as superstition.
In 1939, a girl named Shanti Devi claimed
to be the reincarnation of Lugdibai.
It created a sensation across the country.
A 15 member committee was set up,
to find the truth behind the matter
by the greatest lawyer this nation
has ever produced, Mahatma Gandhi.
He didn't dismiss it as a superstition.
In fact,
according to the commission's findings,
Shanti Devi was indeed
a reincarnation of Lugdibai.
I'm submitting the photographs
and documents related to that case.
There was no scientific proof
in that case either.
Similarly, my client is a reincarnation
of Shyam Singha Roy.
And he rewrote his own stories.
There is no copyright violation
in this case, Your Honor.
Facts can be proved, but this is truth.
It doesn't have any proof.
The final judgment is adjourned
for tomorrow.
After hearing the arguments
from both sides,
due to the lack of logical
and scientific evidence
regarding this case...
Sorry, sir. A small request.
-Who is he?
-He is requesting to meet you.
Let him in.
Considering a personal request
from someone related to this case,
I hereby allow a witness
to appear in the court
before the verdict is delivered.
Uncle?
It's Manoj Roy!
S-Shyam.
Shyam.
Mr. Manoj Singha Roy,
please tell the court
what you want to say about this case.
Vasudev is Shyam Singha Roy.
I believe that my brother, Shyam,
has been reincarnated as Vasu.
I firmly believe it.
He is Shyam Singha Roy.
What are you saying, Uncle?
Silence in the court, please!
Please! Thank you.
Pardon me, Your Honor.
Mr. Roy...
You are claiming that your brother,
Shyam, who died 45 years ago,
has been reincarnated as Vasudev.
You are 85 years old.
It's your belief. Fine!
But why should I, and the honorable judge,
this court, and the public believe you?
Can you give me one good reason why?
Do you have any evidence to prove
that Vasu did not plagiarize
Shyam Singha Roy's stories?
Do you have any substantial proof
of Shyam Singha Roy's reincarnation?
I'm asking you, Mr. Roy. Please tell me.
The court wants to know.
Yes, I have.
I have proof.
A secret which
I was likely to take to my grave,
the venomous side
of the Singha Roy family,
has been revealed by someone in the court.
I was shell-shocked by that.
Anyone can plagiarize
from the published books.
But there's a short story
that has never been published.
And no one knows about its existence,
except for me.
How could Mr. Vasudev make it
as a short film?
Who gave that story to him?
A small story.
The story is...
This is the only copy of that story,
written by Shyam himself.
VARNAM
As the Chairman of SR Publishers,
I withdraw this case.
Because he is not just
the owner of these three stories.
He's the owner of the whole company.
Since the petitioners have withdrawn
the case,
the case is closed.
I didn't lose, but you have won.
Good job.
I'll see you in court again. All the best.
Mannu.
Please forgive me, Shyam.
I was responsible for your death.
I didn't know that our brothers
would do that to you.
You were very stubborn.
That's why you are born again.
Your stories found their way back to you.
Your stories saved you.
This company, all the assets...
It all belongs to you.
Take it.
What should I do with them?
I promised Rosie
that I would spend a lifetime with her.
But I left her midway.
Rosie must have waited for me
until her last breath.
I don't know why I was reborn.
Rosie...
Rosie is alive.
She is waiting for you.
You mean, Rosie...
Is very much alive.
SHYAMA DANCE SCHOOL